forex-go.com 2005-04-19

# ForexGo! - Privacy Policy

Privacy Statement

We are committed to protecting our customers' personal information. In the course of providing you with our products and services, we need to collect and maintain certain non-public personal information about you. This Privacy Statement answers some questions about what non-public personal information we collect, what we do with it, and how we protect it. 

COLLECTING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

When you open and maintain an account with us, we collect the following types of information: 

USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We use your personal information for four primary purposes: 

CONTROL OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may disclose non-public personal information about you that we collect, primarily to make available to you the products and services that we and our business partners provide. We do not disclose non-public personal information about former customers to anyone, except as permitted by law. 

We may disclose certain information about you to our affiliated companies and to other service providers with which we have joint marketing agreements or that offer products and services with us or on our behalf. By sharing information about you and your accounts, transactions, and other customer relationships with our affiliated companies and other service providers, we can provide you with a broader range of products and services, improve your experience with us, and better serve your needs. 

We may also disclose information that we collect from you such as your name, contact information, and customer relationships with us to non-affiliated third parties that perform services for us other than processing or servicing transactions, such as marketing or market research. For example, we may provide your name, address, phone number, and / or e-mail address to vendors who send our e-mail or regular mail. We require that all entities with which we share your non-public personal information, including companies that process or service transactions for us, agree to keep your information confidential. We also prohibit them from using or disclosing your information except for the limited purposes and to the persons for whom disclosure was intended, or as otherwise permitted by law. 

We do not sell your personal information to third-party marketers or any other entity for any purpose. In some limited circumstances, we may disclose non-public personal information about you to a third-party services company, but only with your prior consent (or "opt in"). If you consent (or opt in) to such disclosure, the information shared will be limited to that stated in our request for your consent. 

In addition, we disclose non-public personal information to non-affiliated third parties as permitted or required by law. These parties include government / regulatory organizations such as the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), and Internal Revenue Service (IRS), and to parties under court order or subpoena that request this information. Disclosures for which you have provided your consent or you have directed us to make are also permitted. 

ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your non-public personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time at the Account Center. 

SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We strictly protect the security of your non-public personal information and honor your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under conditions explained above. Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. Your personal information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country where ForexGo.com, its subsidiaries, affiliates or agents are located. 

You also have a significant role in protecting your non-public personal information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your password, so do not share these with others. 

USE OF COOKIES

To ensure we are publishing content customers need and want, ForexGo.com collects aggregated site-visitation statistics using cookies. We do not track individuals' use of the Web Site. When someone visits the site, a cookie is placed on the customer's machine (if the customer accepts cookies) or is read if the customer has visited the site previously. ForexGo.com also uses cookies in connection with the use of your account password on the ForexGo.com Web Site. If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the ForexGo.com Web Site, you will not be able to access the Account Center and the other restricted areas of this Web Site. 

YOUR CHOICE / OPT-OUT

You are given the opportunity to "opt-out" of having your personal information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, we provide an "opt-out" mechanism if you do not wish to receive unsolicited e-mail marketing materials from us and we will take reasonable steps to honor such e-mail opt-out requests. 

YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS

By using this Web Site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Statement. If ForexGo.com updates or changes this Privacy Statement, the changes will be made on this page. Your continued use of this Web Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Statement will mean you accept those changes.
